infopackets.com 2015-05-31

# Infopackets Privacy Policy | www.infopackets.com

Infopackets.com is a free online publication which delivers original, fresh, daily news content based on Microsoft Windows, Internet, technology, and computing trends. If you [subscribe](http://www.infopackets.com/subscribe.htm) to our email newsletter, you can be assured that:

  * Your email address will never be sold, or rented to a third party.
  * You can unsubscribe at any time.
  * Your email address will be kept safe and secure.

All newsletter emails contain [unsubscribe](http://www.infopackets.com/unsubscribe.htm) information at the very bottom of the page. If you have registered a login account with us and you are currently logged in, you can also unsubscribe from [ your user profile page](http://xeon3.infopackets.com/user/).

## The Long Version of our Privacy Policy

Infopackets.com is committed to user privacy in our products and services. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy. Infopackets.com encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all web sites you visit.

Your personal information is used in the following ways:

## User IDs and Passwords

Your user ID and password allows you to login to our system. After you are logged in, you can comment on our articles and access information that would otherwise not be available as an anonymous user.

## Account Information

Your user account tell us who you are, how to contact you, and contains any preferences you have provided, such as language, email format and interests. Some information from your account is viewable by the public, such as your user name, your image profile (if one is uploaded), your birthday (if specified), and the last time you logged in.

## Customer Feedback and Support

The customer feedback mechanism is for requesting information from Infopackets.com. It is used to tell us how we can improve our products, services and similar.

## Email Correspondence

Email correspondence is used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. It is also used to distribute information about Infopackets.com, our products, and services.

## Transactions

Transactions shows which products and services you have requested. We will only use your personal information in the ways specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way in which we use your personal information, unless you consent to the new usage. We will not sell your personal information for third party purposes.

## Security measures

We protect the personal information you share with us. We never store credit card numbers on our web site. Any transactions done through our website are done using third party secure services (such as PayPal, and similar).

## Access to your personal information

Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job. Authorized third party agents may also need access to some of your personal information. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. We only provide third party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We do not otherwise share your personal information with third parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so.

## Data Retention

Infopackets.com will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

## Linked web sites

We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.

## Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

## Cookies

Cookies are used for session management (example: for logging in or out of our site) and allows you to manage your own personal information on the site, such as user name, your profile image, and similar.

## Cookies with Respect to Ads by Google

In association with Google, Inc., we use third-party advertising to serve ads when you visit our website. Some companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Subscribing to our Newsletter

Our email newsletter is delivered daily. Our newsletter delivery system is completely separate from our website 'user account' system; as such, we recommend that you create both a website user account and subscribe to the newsletter at the same time, so that you can respond publicly to our articles when they are delivered to your inbox. To do so:

1\. First, [create a user account](http://xeon3.infopackets.com/user/) by vising the website user account page. Follow the on-screen instructions carefully; a password reset link will be sent to your inbox. Click it, and then set a permanent password for your user account. Once that is complete you can then respond to our artilces publicly. After that, follow on to #2 below.

2\. Next, subscribe to our email newsletter by visiting the [newsletter subscribe page](http://xeon3.infopackets.com/subscribe). By subscribing to our email newsletter, you will always be in touch with the latest headline news in Microsoft Windows, computing, and technoqy trends, plus and frequently asked questions that make our website both popular and unique. Our email newsletter is delivered daily (Monday to Friday) and you can unsubscribe at any time.

## Accessing and Updating User Information

You can make changes to your personal information (such as your email address) by [logging in to our system](http://xeon3.infopackets.com/user/) and editing your user profile preferences. Updating your email address for our newsletter is done in the same manner.

## Unsubscribing from our Newsletter

Each email newsletter has instructions on how to unsubscribe. You can also unsubscribe by visiting our [unsubscribe page](http://www.infopackets.com/unsubscribe.htm).

User Commenting

Infopackets uses a commenting system for its articles. Comments made on our website are seen by the public and will include your account name and a link to your publicly viewable user profile. Not all information about you (via your profile) is accessible to the public.

## Emails to Infopackets with regard to Q&A

We have a large readership of users. Occasionally, we receive really good computer-related questions that we'd like to share with our audience. We therefore reserve the right to re-publish your email (in the form of a question-and-answer, or "Q&A" article) for the sake of sharing knowledge to our community of readers. We will not, however, share your email address or last name in such articles. The only identifiable information about you would be your first name and first initial from your last name. For example, if your name is "John Smith", we may identify you as "John S." in the article.

## Policy updates

All updates to this policy will be posted here.

Last update: January 13, 2015
